https://www.fishfarmermagazine.com/privacy-policy/

The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.
1 About Us
This website www.fishfarmermagazine.com  is owned and operated by Wyvex Media Ltd., a company registered in Scotland no. SC82218 having its registered offices at PO Box 1, Oban, Argyll, PA34 4HB.
Wyvex Media  is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK and we are registered on the Data Protection Public Register number Z5599248
2 Information we collect about You
When you register on our website we may collect your name, email address and other contact details. This allows us to process your registration.
We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically knowingly provide it and have consented to this.
3 What we do with your Information
We use your personal information to update you about new products/services by post, email and/or SMS text message. We will only contact you with your consent.  You are entitled to withhold this consent and opt out from receiving such communications at any time by selecting the appropriate box on the web form that collects your details. You can also update these options by contacting us by email at privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk  or by post to The Data Protection Officer, Wyvex Media Ltd, PO Box 1, Oban, Argyll, PA34 4HB. We will always provide you with a way of opting out of receiving future marketing messages from us, each time we send them to you.
4 Sharing your Information with Third Parties
We may from time to time provide your personal information to third parties for the purposes of providing you with our services. These third party providers include payment processors, providers of card validation services, credit referencing providers and service providers who assist us with hosting our marketing campaigns. They do not decide what is done with your data and only process it on our behalf. These third parties may be located outside the European Economic Area; however we only use providers that provide adequate protection for your information at all times.
We will not for provide your data to other third parties for marketing purposes unless you have specifically consented to this when you first provided your data to us.You are entitled to decline receiving such third party communications by selecting the appropriate box on the web form that collects your details, by contacting us by email at privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk  or by post to  The Data Protection Officer, Wyvex Media Ltd, PO Box 1, Oban, Argyll, PA34 4HB
5 Cookies
This website uses cookies. For more information about what cookies are, what we use them for and how your can delete them, please read our Cookies Policy.
6 How we Protect your Information
We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access to, and loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information in accordance with the UK data protection legislation. These include firewalls and virus checking procedures.
You are responsible for keeping any confidential passwords or other login or access details which you select or which we allocate to you secret. Whilst we take steps to ensure the security of your information, there is a risk that nay information transmitted over the Internet and stored on a computer may be intercepted or accessed by an unauthorised party. If you think that someone has accessed your information held by us without your permission or gained unauthorised access to your login details, you must notify us at privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk
7 Correcting your Information
You are entitled under the GDOR  law to require that we update your personal information to ensure it is up-to-date and accurate. In order to maintain the accuracy of the information we hold, you can update your personal details by sending us an email to privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk
8 Obtaining a copy of your Information
You are entitled to find out what information we hold about you. You can do this by contacting privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk
9 How long we hold your Data for
Some of the information you provide to us will be necessary to carry out repeated tasks, such as verifying your identity or payment details when signing in to use an account or providing our goods and services to you or you using an online checkout. We will keep this information for as long as you remain a registered user of any of our sites and for so long as reasonably necessary.
10 Links to Third Party Websites
Our website contains links to other websites belonging to third parties which are not covered by this privacy policy. If you want to click through to a third party website, please make sure that you read the privacy policy for that website.
11 Updates to this Policy
We may update this Policy at any time without notice. We will tell you that we have updated the policy by emailing you at the email address you have provided to us and/or by posting an announcement on the website. By continuing to use the website after we have emailed you or posted a notice informing you of an update, you accept the changes to this Policy.
12 Contacting Us
If you have any questions about privacy, or wish to update your details or have them removed from our mailing list at any time, please contact us using privacy@wyvexmedia.co.uk
Privacy statement updated May 2018
Click image to readNewsletterStay in touch with the latest developments from Fish Farmer and subscribe to our online updates
Click here to sign up Leave this field empty if you're human: Latest Posts
